bestcouponsforyou.com 2016-02-20

# Get the Best Free Online Coupon Codes and Deals - Best Coupons for You

Privacy Policy 

We appreciate your use our website. The information below explains how Best Coupons for You collects and uses information when you visit our website(s). This Privacy Policy applies to all of Best Coupons for You’s websites including bestcouponsforyou.com.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you continue to use this site this means that you have understood our Privacy Policy and that you agree to the terms. Your use of this website also means that you accept our Terms and Conditions. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the website constitutes your agreements to any changes to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please immediately discontinue any and all use and/or interaction with this website.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at the address provided at the bottom of the page.

What Information Do We Collect? 

We may collect the following personal information from users who use our websites:

  * information that allows us to communicate with you, such as your name, postal addresses, email addresses, social media website account user names, telephone numbers, and/or any other contact information;
  * demographic information including age, gender, geographic area location, and information related to your interests, lifestyle, preference, and coupons that interest you; and
  * information about coupons that you visit or redeem and information related to transactions with merchants and/or business partners that also use our websites.

Certain information such as browser type, domain name and statistics for which pages and deals are being viewer are collected by this website automatically. This is known as “passive information” and is collected from all visitors in on an anonymous basis as you browse the website.

How We Collect Information 

We may ask you for Personal Information when you visit the website. For example, you may be required to provide us with information in order to register for certain services.

We also collect information when you use our website. For example, we may track the coupons you view, submit or redeem, and the content that you submit to the website. We use cookies and related technologies to collect information about your computer and your interaction with the website and our business partner websites. Cookies are small pieces of data that your web browser stores in order to simplify future interactions with a particular website.

If you use a social media platform, a mobile device or other third-party method of communication to interact with Best Coupons for You or our websites, that application may have a specific privacy statement that governs the use of personal information related to that application. For example, if you use a Best Coupons for You mobile application and your mobile device's settings allow it, we may collect information related to your geographical information from your device. Our application may be designed to collect information even if you are not logged into one of our websites. If you have questions about the security and privacy settings of your mobile device, please refer to instructions from your mobile service provider or the manufacturer of your device to learn how to adjust your settings.

We may receive additional information from third parties. For example, we may collect information from third parties to enhance other information we have about you, to help us better understand you, and to otherwise enhance our services.

Email Addresses 

We promise that we will only collect names and email addresses which you have voluntarily supplied to us. We may use this information to distribute newsletters and other similar information.

When we collect your email address and other personal information, we will use this information to deliver you with relevant content, advertising, services, features and any other information that you request. When you supply us with your email address, we might send you emails related to our services or your activity on the website. We might also contact you regarding new services, changes to our website, new features and any other updates that you might find valuable.

Any personal contact information that you supply us with will be used to optimize your experience and improve the quality of your interaction with Best Coupons for You.

How We Use Collected Information 

Best Coupons for You may use information that we collect to:

  * Operate and improve our websites;
  * Provide users with coupons for products and services from participating merchants, including coupons based on variables such as stated and anticipated user interests, personal characteristics, or location;
  * Evaluate the types of coupons, products, or services that may be of interest to users;
  * Track redemption of coupons and perform other analytics;
  * Provide user support, including to our merchants and business partners;
  * Fulfill requests of Best Coupons for You services; and
  * Manage our everyday business needs such as website administration, forum management, analytics, fraud prevention, Terms of Use or to comply with the law.

Sharing Information with Third Parties 

We may share your information with our affiliates, service providers, business partners, and merchants for the purposes described above or to help facilitate the services of our websites. 

We might share your aggregated information about user patterns, habits and characteristics with third parties such as advertisers on your site. This information is anonymous and will not include your personal contact information. We might also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our services and to enhance the website.

We will only share personal contact information volunteered by our users with third parties if we are required to do so by law, if we are required to do so to enforce our Terms of Use or if it is required in order to protect our website, property or trademarks.

Visitors Under the Age of 13 

This site is not intended to be used by anyone under the age of 13 and no person under 13 should disclose any email addresses or personal information on this website. We promise that we will not knowingly obtain personal information from a child under the age of 13. If someone under the age of 13 has provided their personal contact information to this website without guardian consent, the parent or guardian may contact us to have the information removed.

California Privacy 

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California can obtain certain information about the types of personal information that companies with whom they have an established business relationship have shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. In particular, the law provides that companies must inform consumers about the categories of personal information that have been shared with third parties, the names and addresses of those third parties, and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third parties. To request a copy of the information disclosure provided by Best Coupons for You pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact us via email to Lauren [at] bestcouponsforyou.com.

Financial Information 

We do not collect financial information from our users. If you make a financial transaction it is strictly between yourself and the merchant who you are buying goods or services from. Best Coupons for You is not responsible for any financial information that you provide with third party websites. Before providing these third parties with your personal financial information it is recommended that you review their privacy policies.

Contact Information 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or anything else on our website, please don’t hesitate to contact us. We can be reached at this email: Lauren [at] bestcouponsforyou.com.
